Guide to the Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection ca. 1980-1990 MSS.119
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Flyers and Invitations
  - Piezo Electric, undated (Box 3, Folder 366)
  - Pink Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 367)
  - Pindar Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 368)
  - Pizza A Go Go, undated (Box 3, Folder 369)
  - A Place Apart, undated (Box 3, Folder 370)
  - Pleiades Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 371)
  - Plexus, undated (Box 3, Folder 372)
  - Polas Jackson Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 373)
  - Porous, undated (Box 3, Folder 374)
  - Portico, undated (Box 3, Folder 375)
  - Pratt Manhattan Center Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 376)
  - Prince Street Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 377)
  - Private Eyes, undated (Box 3, Folder 378)
  - Protetch McNeil, undated (Box 3, Folder 379)
  - Public Illumination Picture Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 380)
  - The Public Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 381)
  - The Pyramid Club, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 381a)
  - Queens Museum, undated (Box 3, Folder 382)
  - R.H. Love Galleries, undated (Box 3, Folder 383)
  - The Raft Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 384)
  - The Rapp Arts Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 385)
  - Red Parrot, undated (Box 3, Folder 386)
  - Red Wing Performing Group, undated (Box 3, Folder 387)
  - Reinhold-Brown Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 388)
  - Reynold C. Kerr, undated (Box 3, Folder 389)
  - Richard F. Brush Art Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 390)
  - Richard Grey Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 391)
  - River Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 392)
  - Robert Freidus Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 393)
  - Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 394)
  - Robert Streicher Dance Co., undated (Box 3, Folder 395)
  - Roger Litz Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 396)
  - Roger Ramsay Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 397)
  - Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 398)
  - Rosa Esman Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 399)
  - Rotunda Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 400)
  - The Saint, undated (Box 3, Folder 401)
  - St. Clements, undated (Box 3, Folder 402)
  - St. John's in the Village, undated (Box 3, Folder 403)
  - Saint Mark's Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 404)
  - Salander-O'Reilly, undated (Box 3, Folder 405)
  - Salvatore ala, undated (Box 3, Folder 406)
  - Sarah Y. Rentschler Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 407)
  - School of the Art Institute of Chicago Gallery 2, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 407a)
  - Sculpture Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 408)
  - Semaphore Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 409)
  - 77 White Street Gallery Space, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 409a)
  - Sharpe, undated (Box 3, Folder 410)
  - Shelter West, undated (Box 3, Folder 411)
  - Shepherd Gallery Associates, undated (Box 3, Folder 412)
  - Sidewalks Theatre Co., undated (Box 3, Folder 413)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 414)
  - Siegel Contemporary Art, undated (Box 3, Folder 415)
  - 16 Stuyvesant Street, undated (Box 3, Folder 416)
  - Small Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 417)
  - Small Walls, undated (Box 3, Folder 418)
  - The Soho Building, undated (Box 3, Folder 419)
  - Soho Center for Visual Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 420)
  - Soho Photo Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 421)
  - Soho Rep, undated (Box 3, Folder 422)
  - Soho 20 Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 423)
  - Solomon and Co. Fine Art, undated (Box 3, Folder 424)
  - Sonnabend, undated (Box 3, Folder 425)
  - Space, undated (Box 3, Folder 426)
  - Sperone Westwater Fischer, undated (Box 3, Folder 427)
  - Squibb Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 428)
  - Staempfli Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 429)
  - Staley-Wise, undated (Box 3, Folder 430)
  - Stefanotti, undated (Box 3, Folder 431)
  - Stellweg Seguy Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 432)
  - Stewart Neill Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 433)
  - Stonewall Inn, undated (Box 3, Folder 434)
  - Studio 54, undated (Box 3, Folder 435)
  - Studio for the First Amendment, undated (Box 3, Folder 436)
  - The Studio Museum in Harlem, undated (Box 3, Folder 437)
  - Stux Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 438)
  - Susan Caldwell, undated (Box 3, Folder 439)
  - Susan Harder Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 440)
  - 10 on 8, undated (Box 3, Folder 441)
  - Terry Dintenfass, undated (Box 3, Folder 442)
  - Thalia-Soho, undated (Box 3, Folder 443)
  - Thalia-West 95th Street, undated (Box 3, Folder 444)
  - Theatre Development Fund, undated (Box 3, Folder 445)
  - Theatre for a New Audience, undated (Box 3, Folder 446)
  - Theatre in Action, undated (Box 3, Folder 447)
  - Thomas Segal Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 448)
  - Thompson Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 449)
  - 303 Park Ave. South Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 450)
  - Tibor de Nagy Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 451)
  - Tony Shafrazi Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 452)
  - Tracey Garet, undated (Box 3, Folder 453)
  - Tunnel, undated (Box 3, Folder 454)
  - 28th Street Playhouse, undated (Box 3, Folder 455)
  - 25 East 4th Street, undated (Box 3, Folder 456)
  - 22 Wooster Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 457)
  - 225 West Broadway, undated (Box 3, Folder 457a)
  - Two World Trade, undated (Box 3, Folder 458)
  - Tyler Art Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 459)
  - Underground, undated (Box 3, Folder 460)
  - University Art Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 461)
  - University Gallery, University of Mass. @ Amherst, undated (Box 3, Folder 462)
  - University Art Museum-University of New Mexico, undated (Box 3, Folder 463)
  - The University of the Streets, undated (Box 3, Folder 464)
  - University Theater, undated (Box 3, Folder 465)
  - The Urban Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 466)
  - Vanderwoude Tananbaum, undated (Box 3, Folder 467)
  - Video Data Bank, undated (Box 3, Folder 468)
  - Viridian Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 469)
  - Vital Arts Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 470)
  - Warde-Nasse Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 471)
  - Washburn Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 472)
  - Washington Square Church, undated (Box 3, Folder 473)
  - Wave Hill, undated (Box 3, Folder 474)
  - West Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 475)
  - Westbeth Theatre Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 476)
  - Westbroadway Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 477)
  - White Columns, undated (Box 3, Folder 478)
  - White Dog Studio 54 Studio, undated (Box 3, Folder 479)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art Downtown Branch, undated (Box 3, Folder 480)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art Fairfield County, undated (Box 3, Folder 481)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, Madison Avenue, undated (Box 3, Folder 482)
  - Willard Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 483)
  - Women's Interart Center, Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 484)
  - Woods-Gerry Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 485)
  - Wooster Group, undated (Box 3, Folder 486)
  - Workhouse Theater 41, undated (Box 3, Folder 487)
  - Wow Theatre, undated (Box 3, Folder 488)
  - X-Ray Lounge, undated (Box 3, Folder 489)
  - Xavier Fourcade, Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 490)
  - Zabriskie, undated (Box 3, Folder 491)
  - Zim-Lerner Gallery, undated (Box 3, Folder 492)
  - Ken Duncan Photography, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 1a)
  - A.I.R., undated (Box 4, Folder 1, Folder 2 Left)
  - Anthology Film Archives, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bullet Space, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bullet Space Archive, undated (Folder 1 Left)
  - Danceteria, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Deitch Projects, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Friends Roadshow, undated (Folder 4)
  - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Kitchen, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kostabi, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - La Mama, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lace, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Living Theatre Collective, 5, 6, 12, 13 April 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - The Performing Garage, undated (Folder 5)
  - The Pyramid Club, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Roseland, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Saint, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Theatre Laboratoire du danemark, undated (Folder 3 Left)
  - Theatre Plan K, 22 April 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Universal Movement Theatre Repertory, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Unprocessed T-Shirts, undated (Box 5)
- Unprocessed Pins, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)